This chocolate chip cookie dough
blizzard has under 300 calories with 23
g of protein. Let me show you how to
make
it. First, we're going to go in with 400
g of fat-free Fairlife milk combined
with a teaspoon of vanilla extract. And
then here we have 40 to 45 g of a sugar
substitute, 1/4 teaspoon of salt, and
1/4 teaspoon of zantham gum.
And we'll just blend that up and throw
it in our freezer for at least 16
hours. If you guys want to see more
recipes like this, make sure to check
out the link in my bio for my creamy
ebook. It currently has over 30 recipes
and is full of
bangers. Okay, so once that's frozen,
we'll take it out and run it under hot
water for about a minute and then spin
it on light ice cream and then respin
once and then throw in a chocolate chip
cookie and run the mixin setting. And
the consistency should come out
something like this.